I am a dad and I love being a dad I mean
I perform all over the world running all
around the place but I'm a dad first
husband and father that's what it's
[Applause]
about my kids give me all my
material see we had four and five years
so people wonder why I'm a naturally
angry man all of a
sudden but there's just something that
happens when you have four kids in 5
years obviously my wife did you know
everything about that but I was just
sort of there but I'm just telling you
my my family my life with my kids is
awesome but the challenge with these
little ones when they're little you know
your your whole goal is just to not mess
them up to not have them go to jail
someday that's the only real goal that I
have in this life as a dad at this
point you know I mean I don't want them
to be entitled I don't want them to be
that way like we see kids becoming now
and so I guess I'm that
Dad the patient one who sounds
angry want to hear the rest of the joke
click the play button to continue
watching